A Guide to the John K. Martin Records, 1777-1907
Library of Virginia
- Pension Files, 1777-1883 and n.d., 10.62 cubic feet. (Boxes 1-24)
  - Revolutionary War, 1777-1883 and n.d., 2.25 cubic feet. (Boxes 1-5)
    - Revolutionary War - Snead-Spears (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Sorrell, James, 1838, 1852 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Southall, John, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Southall, Turner, 1877 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Spear, John, 1856 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Spears, John, 1853-1854 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Revolutionary War - Spencer-Sutton (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Spencer, Gideon, 1833 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Spitfathom, John, 1851 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Spotswood, Alexander, 1851 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Standley, Moses, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Starkey, William, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Steed, Mark, 1853 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Steigle, Conrad, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Stewart, Samuel, 1855-1859 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Stokes, Richard, 1854 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Sturdivant, John, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Sutton, John, 1851 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Revolutionary War - Taliaferro-Thomas (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Taliaferro, Richard, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Tankard, John, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Taylor, Francis, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Taylor, Richard, 1857, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Taylor, Richard, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Taylor, William, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Templar, Christopher, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Thackston, Benjamin, 1856-1857 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Tharpe, James, 1854 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Thomas, John, 1849 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Thomas, John, 1853-1854 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Thomas, John, 1837, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Revolutionary War - Thompson-Tyree (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Thompson, William, 1855-1856 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Thurston, Charles M., 1877 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Tibbs, John, 1873 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Tincher, Francis, 1866 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Toler, Nehemiah, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Toney, Edmund, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Travis, Champion, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Trevillian, J., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Trexler, Ignatius, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Turpin, John, 1857 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Tyree, James, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Revolutionary War - U (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Upshaw, James, 1857-1858 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Revolutionary War - V (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Valentine, Edward, 1858 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Valentine, Edward, 1869-1876 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Vandewall, Marks, 1870-1877 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Vick, Jesse, 1821-1851 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Revolutionary War - Walker-Watkins (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Walker, Jacob and David, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Wallace, James, 1856 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Watkins, John, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Watkins, John, 1872-1876 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Watkins, John, 1876-1877 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Watkins, John, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Revolutionary War - Watson-White (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Watson, Zackins, 1854 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Waugh, George, 1854 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, Alexander, 1859 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, Richard, 1859 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, William, 1859 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, William, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, William, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, William, 1851-1857 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - White, William, 1858-1859 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Revolutionary War - Wilkins-Wood (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wilkins, James, 1853 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wilkins, Nathaniel, 1851 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Williams, John, 1853-1856 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Williams, John, 1860 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Willis, John W., 1852-1853 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wills, Willis, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wilson, Edward, 1855-1856 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wimbush, John, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Winfield, Curtis, 1852 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Winn, Richard, 1857 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Winter, George, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Withrow, James, 1852 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Wood, Lewis, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Revolutionary War - Woodford-Wright (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Woodford, William, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Woodson, Samuel, 1853-1861 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Woolfolk, William, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Wright, John, 1855-1871 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Wright, Patrick, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Revolutionary War - Y (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Yarborough, Charles, 1857 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Yates, John, 1852 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Revolutionary War - Z (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Zimmerman, Frederick, 1855 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chesapeake-Leopard Affair, 1857-1859 and n.d., .02 cubic feet. (Box 5)
    These are pension files, 1857-1859 and n.d., for claimants with military service during the Chesapeake-Leopard Affair. The Chesapeake-Leopard Affair was a maritime conflict off the coast of Norfolk involving the United States Frigate Chesapeake and the British HMS Leopard. The conflict nearly escalated to war between the two countries in June 1807.
    - Chesapeake-Leopard Affair - Anthony-McRae (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Anthony, James C., 1857 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Barclay, David, 1857-1858 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Davis, Nicholas, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - May, John F., 1859 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - McRae, John, 1859 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - War of 1812, 1812-1883 and n.d., 6.525 cubic feet. (Boxes 6-20)
    These are pension files, 1812-1883 and n.d., for claimants with military service during the War of 1812.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by veteran's surname with individual items within each folder arranged chronologically. Unidentified claimants are arranged chronologically at end of subseries.
    - War of 1812 - Abbott-Baxter (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Abbott, William, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Abernathy, Rawley H., 1855 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Acre, Joshua, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Acre, Leonard, 1854, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Acree, Achiles, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Acree, Ambrose, 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Adams-Alexander (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Adams, James, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Adams, William C., 1855 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Adcock, Samuel, 1850, 1855 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Adkins, George, 1877 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Agnew, James, 1857 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Alderson, Thomas, 1878-1881 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Alexander, William, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Allen-Ammonett (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Abner, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Benjamin, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Allen, James H., 1853-1855 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Ralph, 1851 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Samuel, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Ammonett, Creed, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Alvis-Amos (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Alvis, James, 1858-1874 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Alvis, Joshua, 1856, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Alvis, Walter, 1853-1855 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Alvis, Zephaniah, 1860 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Amos, Pleasant, 1852 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Anderson (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, David, 1855, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Edward, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Edward M., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, George, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, James B., 1856-1857 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Robert, 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Garland, 1855-1879 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, John, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Thomas B., 1856 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, William, 1856-1857 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Andrews-Armstrong (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Andrews, Daniel H., 1851-1879 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Anthony, Mark, 1872, 1876 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Archer, John, 1852-1855 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Armistead, Ralph, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Armstrong, David, 1855 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Arnold-Ashbrook (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Arnold, Henry, 1877-1879 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Arnold, Richard, 1854-1855 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Arthur, Jonas, 1855, 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Ashbrook, William, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Askins-Austin (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Askins, Benjamin, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Aston, Daniel, 1881-1882 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Atkins, William, 1852 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Atkinson, John, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Austin, James, 1852 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Austin, Spotswood, 1857 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Bailey-Baker (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Bailey, Lewis, 1855, 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Baker, R. H., 1850, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Baker, Richard, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Baldwin-Ballow (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Baldwin, William P., 1851-1858 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ballance, Edmund, 1852-1855 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ballow, Charles A., 1852, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ballow, William T., 1855 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Balster-Barnett (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Balster, John, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Banks, William, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Barnes, Joseph, 1851 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Barnett, Elisha, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Barrett-Baxter (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Barrett, Charles, 1879-1880 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Barrott, John H., 1860 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Basket, Reuben, 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Bass, William S., 185- (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Bassener, William H., 1852-1853 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Baugh, Solomon, 1852-1853 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Baughan, James, 1851 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Baughan, William, 1852-1855 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Baxter, James, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - Beasley-Belcher (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Beasley, John, 1853, 1878-1879 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Beasley, Richard, 1852-1853 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Beasley, William, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Beidleman, Valentine, 1882 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Belcher, John, 1876-1877 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Belcher, Edmund, 1857 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Belew-Bentley (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Belew, John, 1853-1854 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bell, William C., 1874-1880 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Belt, Hiram, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bendall, Isaac, 1812-1813, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Benedict, [_] n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Beuham, William, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bentley, [_] 1851 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Berry-Bishop (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Berry, Thomas S., 1881 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Beveridge, William, 1851-1852 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bevil, Branch William, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Binford, John G., 1855 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bingham, Charles, 1878-1879 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Birdsong, John, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bishop, John, 1854 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bishop, Pleasant, 1854 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Blackwell-Boatwright (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blackwell, Benjamin, 1860 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blair, Beverley, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blakey, James, 1879-1880 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blankinship, Benjamin, 1874 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blankinship, Chastain, 1877-1878 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blankinship, Mackness, 1852-1854 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Blunt, James B., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Boatwright, Daniel, 1853-1855 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Booker-Bothwick (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Booker, Richard, 1851-1852, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Booker, William, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Boatwright, William, 1851-1852 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Bothwick, William, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Bottoms-Bradley (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bottoms, Turner, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bougue, Jonathan, 1856-1860 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bowen, James M., 1854 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bowers, Samuel, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bowie, [_] 1878 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bowles, Thomas, 1855-1856 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bradhurst, John M., 1853 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bradley, David, 1855-1857 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bradley, William, 1814 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Bradshaw-Branch (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Bradshaw, James, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Bradshaw, John R., 1876-1877 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Bradshaw, William, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Branch, Christopher, 1852-1857 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Branch, Thomas, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Branch, William, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Bramham-Brooks (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Bramham, Vincent, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Briggs, [_], 1858 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brock, Joseph, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brockenbrough, Arthur S., 1853 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brockenbrough, Austin, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brockwell, John O., 1878 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, Elkanah, 1851-1852, 1875-1879 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, Elkanah, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, Walker, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Browder-Brown (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Browder, Joseph, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, Dudley, 1850-1855 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, Ellis, 1878-1879 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, George, 1878-1879 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, John, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, John B., 1852, 1854 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, Joseph, 1860 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Brown, Robert, 1877 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Browning-Bullock (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Browning, Gehu, 1851-1852 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Brummall, Bernard, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Bryan, Wilson, 1859 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Buckner, Charles, 1858 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Buckner, William, 1854 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Bull, John, Sr. 1873 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Bullard, John, 1858, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Bullock, David B., 1850, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Bullock, John, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Burchell-Butler (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burchell, William W., 1851 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burk, John J., 1853-1854 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, Benjamin, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, Benjamin M., 1855-1856 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, John, 1853 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, John P., 1851 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, Reuben, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, Thomas, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burton, William, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burts, John, 1881 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Burwell, Lewis, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Butler, Overton, 1858 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Caid-Calhoun (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Caid, [_], 1853 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Calhoun, Patrick, 1855-1857 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Calhoun, Patrick, 1857-1859 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Camden-Cary (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Camden, Jordan P., 1852 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Campbell, John, 1853 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Campbell, William, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Cardwell, Richard L., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Carr, Dabney, 1858 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Carrington, George, 1851 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Carrington, John B., 1850-1855 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Carter, Alexander, 1852-1853 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Carter, Thomas M., 1879-1880 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Cary, Samuel, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Cassell-Cheatham (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Cassell, John, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Caufield, William, 1855 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chandler, Smallwood, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chalkley, Spencer, 1855, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chancellor, Joshua, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Charter, George, 1856 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Cheatham, Francis, 1851-1852 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Cheatham, Joseph, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Cheatham, Isham, 1852-1856 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Chenault-Christian (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Chenault, Burton, 1838, 1855 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Chenault, Thomas, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Childress, John, 1851 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Childress, Patrick, 1854-1860 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Childress, William, 1851 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Christian, Edmund, 1856 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Christian, James, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Christian, [_], 1882 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Clark, Hatcher-Clark, John (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Clark, Hatcher, 1878-1879 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Clark, Jeremiah, 1852 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Clark, John, January-November 1879 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Clark, John, November 1879-February 1880 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Clark, John-Clowe (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clark, John, March-May 1880 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clark, John, June 1880-July 1882 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clark, Samuel, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clark, William, 1854-1856 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clasby, William, 1852-1853 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clowe, Charles B., 1875-1877 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Coates-Cockburn (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Coates, Joseph, 1851-1855 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Cobb, Jeremiah, 1850 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Cobb, John, 1856 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Cockburn, Alexander, 1855-1856 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Cogbill-Cook (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Cogbill, Edward H., 1851-1852 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Cole, John G., 1856 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Coleman, Elijah, 1857 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Coleman, Wyatt, 1858-1859 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Collier, Benjamin, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Collins, Charles, 1878-1879 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Condrey, Joshua, 1852 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Cook, Lawrence C., 1854 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Corker-Courtney (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Corker, Daniel, 1878-1879 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Cottrell, William, 1853-1857 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Coults, Patrick, 1852-1878 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Courtney, James, 1860 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Cowles-Crawford (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Cowles, Thomas, 1852, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Cox, James, 1859 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Cox, Obediah, 1853-1854 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Crane, Jonas, 1850 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Crawford, James, 1878-1880 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Crenshaw-Crouch, Rolly (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Crenshaw, Freeborn G., 1854, 1878-1879 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Crisp, John, 1858-1859 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Crittendon, William G., 1856 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Cross, Reuben, 1855-1856 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Cross, Richard, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Crouch, Joseph R., 1851 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Crouch, Rolly, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Crouch, Thomas-Crump, Joshua (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Crouch, Thomas H., 1878-1879 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Crowdis, Miles, 1878-1880 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Crump, Henry, 1856-1857 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Crump, Jessie, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Crump, Joshua P., 1851-1881 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Crump, Sterling, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Crumpler, Dempsey M., 1851-1852 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Crutchly, Benjamin, 1851-1858 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Curtis, William H., 1856 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Dabney, Joseph F., 1880 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Daugherty-Denton (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Daugherty, James, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Davenport, Joshua, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Davenport, Richard, 1851, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Davenport, William, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Davis, Hugh, 1853 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Davis, Isaac, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Dean, Christopher P., 1852 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Delbridge, Warren, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Denton, Allen, 1878-1879 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Derrough-Dorrington (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Derrough, William, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Devers, Thomas, 1880 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Dickinson, Riddick, 1858 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Divine, Joseph, 1854-1855 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Dobbin, Robert, 1852, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Donly, John, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Dorrington, David, 1851, 1852 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Drabell-Drewry, Martin (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Drabell, John, 1851-1853 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Drake, William, 1853-1855, 1880 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Drewry, Henry, 1878-1879 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Drewry, Martin, 1858 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Dudley-Duke (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Dudley, George F., 1871-September 1880 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Dudley, George F., September 1880-January 1881 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Dudley, George F., February 1881-1883 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Duke, Benjamin, 1882 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Dunkum-Dupey (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Dunkum, David, 1851-May 1853 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Dunkum, David, June 1853-April 1854 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Dunkum, David, May 1854-1856 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Dunnavant, William W., 1855, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Dupey, Anthony M., 1857 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Durfey-Easley (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Durfey, William, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Duval, John P., 1852 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Dyer, Benjamin, 1822, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Dyer, Frank, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Earnest, William, 1856-1858 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Easley, Henry, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Edwards-Elam (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Edwards, Williams, 1857, 1878-1881 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Eggleston, Richard B., 1878-1880 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Elam, Branch, 1820 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Elam, Roland, 1877-1880 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Elam, William G., 1855-1856 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Elder-Elliott, Robert (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Elder, Daniel C., 1860 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Ellett, James B., 1857 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Ellington, John, 1821, 1845-1853 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Ellington, John, 1854-1857 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Elliott, Robert, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Elliott, Thomas-Emery, Claiborne (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Elliott, Thomas, 1879, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Ellis, Francis R., 1852, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Ellis, John W., 1854 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Ellis, Stephen B., 1851-1855 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Ellis, William, 1857 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Ellis, William B., 1851-1854 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Emery, Claiborne, 1854-1855 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Emery, David-Epps (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - Emery, David, 1856 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Emmerson, Arthur, 1851 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Emmery, John, 1853-1855 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - England, John, 1871 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - English, John, 1860-1877 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Epps, Edwards, 1858 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Errington-Estes (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Errington, Lewis, 1815 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Erambut, Henry, 1856, 1878-1879 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Espey, Samuel, 1852 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Estes, Christopher T., 1878-1880 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - Eubank, George-Eubank, John (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Eubank, George, 1881-1882 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Eubank, Hezekiah, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Eubank, John, March 1882-August 1882 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Eubank, John, 1879-March 1882 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Eubank, John-Farguson (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Eubank, John, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)